rahim-soft.com 2017-05-23

# Privacy Policy - Rahim soft

Last Updated: 28th July, 2016, 6:39 PM

Please read this Privacy policy carrefully. Is available using our site. For any further informations we can be contacted via e-mail (see the link Contact us)

**Collection of Information about your personal datas or informations**  
During you are surfing our site ,we collect personally identifiable information such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc. and informations about your computer details like IP , browser,operating system, country,speed of Internet .Some of these datas are voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. The informations you provide to us are not used in other manner that is described in the contact forms.Navigating these pages you can use all informations just for personal use ,not for commercial one.

**Cookie and Tracking Technology**  
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and [content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

The freedownloadsplace.com may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered.It doesn’t matter if you are getting a product or not. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

[Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense/) is using cookies to collect data from your computer.Reading this page you automatically agree with these cookies.

For any further informations you can contact us using email communication [here](http://rahim-soft.com/contact-us).
